

export const objectOfNumbers = {'ONE': 'ONE', 'TWO': 'TWO', 'THREE': 'THREE', 'FOUR': 'FOUR', 'FIVE': 'FIVE', 'SIX': 'SIX'};

export const questionsAnswers = {
  q0: {question: "nothing",
  answers: ['nothing', 'nothing', 'nothing'],
  answer: 'nothing'
  },
  q1: {question: "George Washington was a member of what society named after which individual who served as Roman Consul?",
  answers: ['Cincinnatus', 'Aurelius', 'Cassius'],
  answer: 'Cincinnatus'
  },
  q2: {question: "Born into slavery, Robert Smalls freed himself and other slaves by sailing which Confedarate ship from Charleston Harbor into the Union blockade?",
  answers: ['CSS Planter', 'CSS John Calhoun', 'CSS Afrique'],
  answer: 'CSS Planter'
  },
  q3: {question: "Confederate general James Longstreet is viewed as what to admirers of the Confederacy?",
  answers: ['a hero', 'a scalawag', 'a carpet bagger'],
  answer: 'a scalawag'
  },
  q4: {question: "What untrained historian wrote several acclaimed histories, including 'The Guns of August'?",
  answers: ['Barbara Tuchman', 'Eleanor Roosevelt', 'Helen Thomas'],
  answer: 'Barbara Tuchman'
  },
  q5: {question: "Which institution was a major source of credit to antebellum enslavers and cotton producers?",
  answers: ['JP Morgan', 'Brown Brothers', 'Credit Suisse'],
  answer: 'Brown Brothers'
  },
  q6: {question: "Which Revolutionary War figure and Virginian uttered the words 'Give me liberty, or give me death!'?",
  answers: ['James Monroe', 'George Mason', 'Patrick Henry'],
  answer: 'Patrick Henry'
  },
  q7: {question: "Franklin, Tennessee is named for this man who was partner in the largest internal slave trading firm in the country.",
  answers: ['Benjamin Franklin', 'Franklin Templeton', 'Isaac Franklin'],
  answer: 'Isaac Franklin'
  },
  q8: {question: "Under Lord Dunmore's command, the British Fleet unloaded on and set ablaze this coastal Colonial city.",
  answers: ['Norfolk', 'Baltimore', 'Jersey City'],
  answer: 'Norfolk'
  },
  q9: {question: "This famed civil rights leader passed away on July 17, 2020, the same day that his colleague in the struggle, John Robert Lewis, passed.",
  answers: ['Hosea Lorenzo Williams', 'Cordy Tindell Vivian', 'Joseph Echols Lowery'],
  answer: 'Cordy Tindell Vivian'
  },
  q10: {question: "After taking and passing the New York bar exam during his third year of law school, FDR dropped out and never graduated from which law school?",
  answers: ['Yale', 'Columbia', 'Harvard'],
  answer: 'Columbia'
  },
  q11: {question: "The free Black population in America roughly numbered when Southern states began seceding from the Union?",
  answers: ['500,000', '1,000,000', '1,500,00'],
  answer: '500,000'
  },
  q12: {question: "Confederate General Jubal Early's command and the Shenandoah Valley both found ruin at the hands of this Union general.",
  answers: ['John Pope', 'Benjamin Butler', 'Philip Sheridan'],
  answer: 'Philip Sheridan'
  },
  q13: {question: "Contrary to initial reports, President Harry Truman did indeed defeat this man in the 1948 presidential contest.",
  answers: ['Thomas Dewey', 'Wendell Willkie', 'Adlai Stevenson II'],
  answer: 'Thomas Dewey'
  },
  q14: {question: "Who was Francis Scott Key's friend and brother-in-law?",
  answers: ['John Wilkes Booth', 'Stephan Douglas', 'Roger Taney'],
  answer: 'Roger Taney'
  },
  q15: {question: "Serving symbolically for just twenty-four hours, she, nevertheless, was the first woman to serve in the Senate.",
  answers: ['Rebecca Latimer Felton', 'Tallulah Bankhead', 'Hattie Caraway'],
  answer: 'Rebecca Latimer Felton'
  }
};